honorsociety.org 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy | Honor Society

Effective on January 17, 2014

We at HonorSociety.org know that your privacy is important. This privacy policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we will collect and use the information you provide when you use our Website. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we collect and use your information. If we make any material changes to this privacy policy, we will notify you in accordance with the process described in the Changes section of this privacy policy.  By using our Website, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your information as described in this privacy policy. 

This privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Information We Collect

### Information We Automatically Collect.

When you access our Website whether by computer, mobile phone or other device, we automatically collect certain information about your use of our Website (this information may include without limitation: geographical location and IDs of your computer, mobile or other device; bandwidth used;  system and connection performance; browser type and version, operating system; referral source; length of visit;  page views;  referral source; IP address or other unique identifier for your computer, mobile phone or other device; your mobile carrier) using technologies, such as Cookies and web beacons. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Information You Provide To Us.

In some situations you may provide us with your personal identifying information (called “PII”) PII could include your name, street address, telephone number, email address, answer to security questions, graduation date, profile photograph and, if necessary, social security number, driver’s license number, date of birth and credit card and/or other payment/ordering information and any other information we collect about you that by itself is not PII but if combined with PII could be used to personally identify you.

You may provide us with PII when you:   
enter a sweepstakes or contest,  
complete a survey,  
make a purchase,  
subscribe to our Website services, email notifications and/or newsletters,  
register for certain services, or register and/or set up an account/profile to access, visit and/or use certain portions of our Website  
provide comments, reviews, feedback, or testimonials about our Website or products or services  
any other transactions between you and us on or in relation to our Website

### Refer a Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our Website we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  
We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email, tracking the success of our referral program, and following up with additional information if your friend opts in to receiving information from us.

Your friend may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#dab7bfb7b8bfa8a9bfa8acb3b9bfa99ab2b5b4b5a8a9b5b9b3bfaea3f4b5a8bd) to request that we remove this information from our database.  
Treatment of your friend’s information will be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

### Cookies

A “Cookie” is a small file stored on your hard drive that contains information about your computer. We may use Cookies to enable us to track and target your interests for the purpose of enhancing your experience on our Website. By showing how and when visitors use the Site, cookies help us deliver advertisements, identify how many unique users visit us, save user preferences and track user trends and patterns. We use:

Session Cookies which are Cookies that are deleted when you leave our Website.  
Persistent Cookies which are Cookies that remain after you leave our Website so that you are recognized when you return.

The use of Cookies is industry standard so your browser may be set to accept cookies. If you would prefer not to accept cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to reject all Cookies or some Cookies. Note, if you reject certain Cookies, you may not be able to access all of our Website features.

Our Website may also contain third-party cookies from advertising partners. To opt-out of these type of cookies, visit the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by visiting [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). Even if you opt-out through the NAI website, you can still receive communications you have signed up to receive from us unless you opt out of those by using the information in the Opting-Out and Updating Your Information sections of this privacy policy.

### Web Beacons

We may use web beacons (also known as clear GIFs.) to access Cookies and count users who visit our Website or open our HTML-formatted e-mail messages. Web beacons are single-pixel graphic files with a unique identifier, similar to Cookies. Web beacons are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are stored on a user's hard drive. You can modify your browser settings to control web beacons.

## How We Use Your Information

### HonorSociety.org will use Information we Automatically Collect to:

Improve your experience on our Website and our services, to count users who visit our Website or open our HTML-formatted e-mail messages, improve the delivery of our ads and web pages to you help us better manage content on our Website by informing us what content is effective and by helping to measure traffic on our Website.

We may use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Web site, analyze trends, track users' movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the Website, and deliver customized content.

### HonorSociety.org will use PII to:

respond to your inquiries, and/or other requests or questions  
enable your use of the services available on our Website  
contact you regarding your purchase  
collect payments from you

and to send you:  
goods or services purchased through our Website  
information and updates related to your purchase  
invoices  
email notifications which you have specifically requested  
email marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you  
email messages containing company news, product or service information  
and certain email marketing communications relating to third parties such as: our affiliates

### Sharing PII with Third Parties

We may use third parties to perform certain services on our behalf. We may share your PII including payment card information, with these third parties solely to enable them to perform the services for us.

Such third parties include those:

hosting our Website  
managing the functionality of our Website  
processing credit or other payment card payments  
fulfilling and processing orders  
delivering products you have ordered  
assisting with promotions              
enabling us to send you e-mail

We require that those third party vendors maintain at least the same level of confidentiality that we maintain for such information.  We do not provide your PII to parties unconnected with the services we provide. Your information will not be sold to nor will it be exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering a product or service.

## Security

HonorSociety.org has implemented and follows commercially reasonable measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of PII. Unfortunately, data transmission over the Internet is never 100% secure so we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or from our Website therefore you use our Website at your own risk.

If you register on our Website you are responsible for protecting the security of your user name and password. You are responsible for any transaction made using your user name and password.

We use industry standard security measures. All credit card information you submit via our Website is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption.

All payments submitted through our Website are processed by our payment processor Authorize.net. You can review the Authorize.net privacy policy at: [http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy](https://www.authorize.net/company/privacy). We will share information with Authorize.net to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds.

### Posting In Public Areas Of Our Website

You may choose to participate in our message boards, chat rooms and other public areas (together “Public Spaces”) where you can engage in social networking, interact with others, and submit writings, music, video and/or audio recordings, computer graphics, pictures, questions, comments, testimonials, suggestions or other content, including PII. If there is information that you do not wish to disclose to everyone we suggest you do not post it.  Anything you post to Public Spaces on our Website is public. Others will be able to view and access it and they may be able to use it and share it with third parties. The protections of this privacy policy will not cover your disclosure of information or content in Public Spaces. Carefully consider anything you intend to post before you post and use caution.

### Testimonials

We may select and post customer testimonials on our Website which may contain PII such as your name and/ or the city, state, or country in which you live. We encourage you to create an anonymous unidentifiable screen name when posting testimonials.

When submitting your testimonial you are giving us permission to post your testimonial on our Website.

If you post such content, it will be available to other users of the Website. Your posting may also become public and we cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate our Privacy Policy or the law.

If you would like us to remove or delete your name or testimonial from our Website, you may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#2d4048404f485f5e485f5b444e485e6d454243425f5e424e4448595403425f4a).

Note that copies of information that you have updated, modified or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of our Website for a period of time.

### Reviews

We may select and post customer reviews on our Website which may contain PII such as your name and/ or the city, state, or country in which you live. We encourage you to create an anonymous unidentifiable screen name when posting reviews.

When submitting your review you are giving us permission to post your review on our Website.

If you post such content, it will be available to other users of the Website. Your posting may also become public and we cannot prevent such information from being used in a manner that may violate our Privacy Policy or the law.

If you would like us to remove your name or review from our Website, you may contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#4d2028202f283f3e283f3b242e283e0d252223223f3e222e2428393463223f2a).

Note that copies of information that you have updated, modified or deleted may remain viewable in cached and archived pages of our Website for a period of time.

## Links To Third Party Websites

Our Website may contain links to third party content or Websites that HonorSociety.org does not control. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners. NOTE: if you click on these links and enter a third party’s Website these third parties may use their own Cookies to collect data or solicit PII. You should read the third party Website’s privacy policy to learn how they will collect and use your information as their policies may differ from ours and will apply to your use of their Website.

Our Website makes it easy for you to access social media with features such as a ShareThis button, widgets, and other interactive programs. These features may collect your IP address, track which page you are visiting on our Website, and set Cookies. Treatment of any information shared with third party Websites when you use these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing them.

HonorSociety.org is not responsible for the treatment of your PII or any of your information by any third party.

## Opting Out and Changing Or Updating Your Information

You may opt-out of having your PII shared with third parties for reasons other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested and except as required by law and you may also request updates or changes to your information or your preferences regarding receiving future promotional messages from us. To do this you may contact our Privacy Officer using the information in the Contact Us section of this privacy policy.

Please note that if you opt-out of promotional/marketing emails, you may continue to receive certain communications from us, such as administrative and services announcements and/or messages about your account/profile.

### Changing or Updating Your Information

You can review and change or update personal information you have provided and your subscriptions or preferences regarding information you receive from us by logging in to your account and making or requesting changes.  We will implement your requested changes as soon as we reasonably can. When you edit your information or change your preferences, information that you remove may remain in our databases or backup media because it is not always possible to completely remove or delete information from those locations. If you have made any postings in a Public Space of our Website, these cannot generally be removed.

## Sharing Your Information

We may disclose your PII (a) to extent required by law or if we have a good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to comply with official investigations or legal proceedings initiated by governmental and/or law enforcement officials, or private parties, including but not limited to: in response to subpoenas, search warrants, or court orders or (b) if we sell or transfer all or a portion of our company’s business interests, assets, or both, or in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, or other company change or (c) to our subsidiaries or affiliates only if necessary for business and operational purposes or (d) to our vendors if necessary in order to provide you with service as further described below.

Without your express consent, your information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other entity, other than companies acting as our agents to perform task(s) on our behalf and under our instructions, for any reason that is not compatible with the reason that you originally shared the information (except as described above).

We may use third party vendors to perform certain services on our behalf, such as hosting our Website, maintaining, enhancing, or adding to the functionality of our Website, operating our Website’s features, processing payment card payments, fulfilling and processing orders, assisting with promotions, tracking analytics, enabling us to send you e-mail, or performing other administrative services. We may share your PII including payment card information, with these third party vendors solely to enable them to perform the services for us. In providing such information, we require that those third party vendors maintain at least the same level of confidentiality that we maintain for such information.  We do not provide your PII to parties unconnected with the services we provide.

We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data, which does not include any PII, about our Website users as a group for any legal business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers, sponsors, clients and customers.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

## Child Privacy

This Website is not directed at, or intended for use by, children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly allow anyone under 18 to provide any personal information on our Website. Children should always get permission from a parent or guardian before sending personal information over the Internet. If you believe your child may have provided us with personal information, you can contact our Privacy Officer using the information in Contact Us section of this privacy policy and we will delete the information.

## Changes To This Policy

We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our Website. You should visit this page occasionally to ensure you agree with any changes.  We will post our revised privacy policy on our Website and update the "Effective" date above to reflect the date of the changes. You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided as part of registration.

By continuing to use our Website after we post any such changes, you accept the privacy policy as modified.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your information, please write to us our Privacy Officer by email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#fe939b939c9b8c8d9b8c88979d9b8dbe969190918c8d919d979b8a87d0918c99)

or by postal mail at

Attn: Privacy Officer  
10100 W. Charleston Blvd., Ste. 250  
Las Vegas, Nevada 89135

If you need to communicate with us regarding your credit card or other payment information please contact us by phone at our designated customer support number. Do not include any account numbers in your email as email is not a secure form of communication.
